

NGUYỄN DIỆU HƯƠNG Software Developer / Translator / Editor

9/4/1999

8

0961578499

dieuhuong2h@outlook.com

🚹 101A Phuong Mai, Ha Noi

https://aislingvt.vercel.app/res ume?cv=huong

Skills

HTML, CSS, SCSS



English



JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJs, Git, Figma, NextJS



Java, Python, JSP, Postman, Firebase, JSON, BIRT report, Angular, SQL



Vue, C#, MongoDBXML, JQuery, NodeJs



My Language skill: C1
English (proficient), N5
Japanese

OBJECTIVE

I have been designing and creating websites for over 2 years. I have experience designing and writing websites mainly in ReactJS, and have a creative mind. If you want to boost your business with a great React website, then let's talk!

I'm looking to join an inclusive company which doesn't discriminate peoples based on their race / gender / culture as a freelancer / salaryperson!

My English proficiency includes good communication skills in both listening and speaking, and the ability to read and write documents in English.

Additionally, I am proficient in using project management tools such as Git, IDEs such as Visual Studio Code, and various designer tools such as Photoshop, Figma, and can do a bit of sound / video editing!

EDUCATION

09/2017 - 4/2023

FPT UNIVERSITY - HOA LAC | Software Engineering Major Bachelor's degree certificates. GPA: 6,94

WORK EXPERIENCES

04/2023 - 09/2024

WORKING AT FPT FIS (1+ YEAR) | Fresher / Employee

- I gained valuable experience collaborating and contributing effectively as part of a team, working on both front-end and back-end tasks.
- I honed my skill in React.js development and experienced in utilizing various other front-end tools, backed by practical work experience in a professional setting.

04/2022 - 07/2022

3 MONTHS OF FRESHER AT CMC GLOBAL | Fresher

- During this job, I became familiar with corporate procedures and completed online courses to enhance my skills.
- Additionally, I gained valuable insight into teamwork and developed the ability to effectively contribute as a member of a team. I also involved with a project to enhance my ReactJS / NextJS skill.

01/2020 - 07/2022

3 MONTHS OF INTERNSHIP AT FSOFT | Intern

- I had the opportunity to immerse myself in various office tasks and environments, allowing me to gain valuable work experience, learn about work ethics and responsibilities.
- I also had the chance to work with tools like Git and utilize popular Integrated Development Environments (IDEs) such as NetBeans, VSCode, and PyCharm, which provided me with valuable hands-on experience.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

I'm Able to work with Different object-oriented programming languages such as Python, Java, Typescript,...

I'm Familiar with project management models such as SCRUM, AGILE,

My Language skill: C1

English (proficient), N5 Japanese wateriai

I'm capable of Using Project management tools like Github, Gitlab or Git, and willing to learn different tools.

I'm also a quick learner, and capable of using different Al tools like Chatgpt, characterAl and more

I have skills in video editing using Wondershare Filmora, and have some photoshop skills, and Audio editing skills using Audacity.

SOFT SKILLS & QUALITIES

My Language skill: C1 English (proficient), N5 Japanese

I have Proficient English skills, knowledgeable in using writing tools, such as Grammar.ly,...

An example of my writings: https://shorturl.at/DmegC

Although A bit introverted, when it comes to work ethics, I'm meticulous and observant about any assigned task, and persistent in getting works done.

I'm Able to work both independently or in a team environment.

PROJECTS

-

THESE ARE MY PERSONAL PROJECTS, PROJECTS THAT I HAVE PARTAKEN IN DURING MY WORKEXPERIENCE AND OTHER PROJECTS DURING MY UNIVERSITY EDUCATION:

- Developed a user management web front using ReactJS for Dat Xanh Group: http://uat-admin.datxanh.com.vn/
- Blogging website (registered domain): https://duyhung2h.web.app/, written in ReactJs.
- Blogging website (registered domain): https://aislingvt.vercel.app/, written in ReactJs + NextJS + Vercel.
- Comic reading website: A Frontend project for reading different comics
- House rental website: A simple Frontend project for landlords to manage financial details.
- Nhà Hàng Ba Miền website: A Fullstack website platform for customers and managers, specialising in online food delivery
- Black League Shop website: A Fullstack website shoe shop platform for customers
- Project André: A Python project for my upcoming modded game project

MORE INFO

All of my different day-to-day hobbies!

- Playing and modifying video games
- Reading, writing in English
- History, world's cultures and geography

- Listening to podcasts and music
- Painting and arts

© topcv.vn